Guide to the Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theater Records, 1934-1994 CTC.1981.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Business and Financial Records, 1944-1973; II.
  - Box Office Reports - MacBeth, 1947 (Box 47C, Folder 24)
  - Box Office Reports - The Mad Show, 1966 (Box 47C, Folder 25)
  - Box Office Reports - Magic Horn, 1970 (Box 47C, Folder 26)
  - Box Office Reports - Man of La Mancha, 1972 (Box 48A, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Man's a Man, 1966 (Box 48A, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - Mary Mary, 1965 (Box 48A, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - Merchant of Venice, 1972 (Box 48A, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1967 (Box 48A, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - My Three Angels, 1954 (Box 48A, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - Mystery at Crooked Pine Ranch, 1969 (Box 48A, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - Mystery at the Old Fort, 1969 (Box 48A, Folder 8)
  - Box Office Reports - National Theater of the Deaf, 1970 (Box 48A, Folder 9)
  - Box Office Reports - Never Too Late, 1972 (Box 48A, Folder 10)
  - Box Office Reports - No Strings, 1971 (Box 48A, Folder 11)
  - Box Office Reports - Noah, 1965 (Box 48A, Folder 12)
  - Box Office Reports - Nutcracker Ballet, 1968 (Box 48A, Folder 13)
  - Box Office Reports - Nutcracker Ballet, 1969 (Box 48A, Folder 14)
  - Box Office Reports - Owl and the Pussycat, 1969 (Box 48A, Folder 15)
  - Box Office Reports - Odd Couple, 1968 (Box 48A, Folder 16)
  - Box Office Reports - The Panda and the Spy, 1951 (Box 48A, Folder 17)
  - Box Office Reports - Papa Pampino and the Prize Fighter, 1955 (Box 48A, Folder 18)
  - Box Office Reports - Payment Deferred, 1953 (Box 48A, Folder 19)
  - Box Office Reports - Peg O' My Heart, 1952 (Box 48A, Folder 20)
  - Box Office Reports - Pied Piper of Hamlin, 1954 (Box 48B, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Pied Piper of Hamlin, 1966 (Box 48B, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - Pinter Plays, 1969 (Box 48B, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - Pittsburgh ballet, 1970 (Box 48B, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - Pinocchio, 1966 (Box 48B, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - Play It Again Sam, 1972 (Box 48B, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - Playhouse Follies, 1964 (Box 48B, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - Playhouse Jr. 1952/1953 season (Box 48B, Folder 8)
  - Box Office Reports - Playhouse Jr. 1951/1952 season (Box 48B, Folder 9)
  - Box Office Reports - Playhouse Jr. 1951/1952 season (Box 48B, Folder 10)
  - Box Office Reports - Plaza Suite, 1972 (Box 48B, Folder 11)
  - Box Office Reports - Poor Nut, 1947 (Box 48B, Folder 12)
  - Box Office Reports - Present Laughter, 1951 (Box 48B, Folder 13)
  - Box Office Reports - Prime of Miss Jean Brodie, 1973 (Box 48B, Folder 14)
  - Box Office Reports - Pro Musica, 1969 (Box 48B, Folder 15)
  - Box Office Reports - Box Office Reports - Rapunzel and the Witch, 1973 (Box 48B, Folder 16)
  - Box Office Reports - Red Juice, 1971 (Box 48B, Folder 17)
  - Box Office Reports - The Rivers, 1973 (Box 48B, Folder 18)
  - Box Office Reports - Remains To Be Seen, 1952 (Box 48B, Folder 19)
  - Box Office Reports - Rhinoceros, 1965 (Box 48B, Folder 20)
  - Box Office Reports - Robinson Crusoe, 1966 (Box 48B, Folder 21)
  - Box Office Reports - Room Service, 1971 (Box 48B, Folder 22)
  - Box Office Reports - Rose Tattoo, 1965 (Box 48B, Folder 23)
  - Box Office Reports - Royal Family, 1953 (Box 48B, Folder 24)
  - Box Office Reports - Rumpelstiltskin, 1969 (Box 48B, Folder 25)
  - Box Office Reports - Salvation, 1972 (Box 48C, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Season 1948/1949 (Box 48C, Folder 2-3)
  - Box Office Reports - Season 1949/1950 (Box 49A, Folder 1-3)
  - Box Office Reports - Season 1950/1951 (Box 49A, Folder 4-5)
  - Box Office Reports - Season 1950/1951 (Box 49B, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Season 1951/1952 (Box 49B, Folder 2-4)
  - Box Office Reports - Season 1952/1953 (Box 49B, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - Season 1953/1954 (Box 49B, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - Season 1953/1954 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Season 1954/1955 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - The Serpent, 1969 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - Servant of Two Masters, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - She Loves Me, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - Sinbad, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - Six Characters in Search of an Author, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - Sleeping Beauty, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Box Office Reports - Star Spangled Girl, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Box Office Reports - Streetcar Named Desire, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Box Office Reports - Streets of New York, 1970 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Box Office Reports - Tartuffe, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Box Office Reports - Theatre Upstairs, 1964-65 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Box Office Reports - Thousand Clowns, 1964 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Box Office Reports - Three One-Acts, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Box Office Reports - Three Sisters, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Box Office Reports - Tiny Alice, 1965 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Box Office Reports - Titian, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Box Office Reports - Tom Paine, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Box Office Reports - Tom Sawyer's Treasure Hunt, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Box Office Reports - Twentieth Century, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Box Office Reports - Two for the Seesaw, 1967 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Box Office Reports - Typists and the Tiger, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Box Office Reports - Vince Burrows, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Box Office Reports - Voice of the Turtle, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Box Office Reports - Wait Until Dark, 1969 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Box Office Reports - Water Witch, 1951 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Box Office Reports - White Sheep of the Family, 1955 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Box Office Reports - White Steed, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Box Office Reports - Who's Afraid of Virginia Woolf, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Box Office Reports - Woman in the Dunes, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Box Office Reports - Wonderful Good, 1952 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Box Office Reports - You Can't Take It With You, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Box Office Reports - Your Own Thing, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Budget - Notes and Projections, 1967-1969 (Box 52, Folder 1-2)
  - Budget - School and Playhouse Jr., 1965 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Budget - Summary, 1959-1967 (Box 52, Folder 4-5)
  - Budget - Summary of Working Capital, 1966-1967 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Budget, April 1972 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Budget, May 1972 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Budget, June 1972 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Building Fund statements, 1949-1952 (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Cash balance, August 15, 1966 (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Cash flow, 1968 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Cash position, October 1966 (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Chart of Accounts, July 1967 (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Chart of Accounts, January 1972 (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Chart of Accounts - General Ledger, February 1972 (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Chart of Accounts, 1969-1971 (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Chart of Accounts, 1971-1972 (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Chart of Accounts, July 1968 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Chart of Accounts, July 1967 (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Chart of Accounts - Productions, 1971-1973 (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Comparative Balance sheets, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Contributions, 1967-1968 (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Cost areas, 1971-1972 (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Deferred Income (Account #2), 1973 (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Building fund pledge sheets, 1949-1950 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Cash receipts and disbursements, 1956-1958 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Cash receipts and disbursements, 1971-1973 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Check Stubs - Operating account, 1972-1974 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Check Stubs - Deferred account, 1973-1974 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Check Stubs - Expenses, 1970-1971 (Box 56A, Folder 1-3)
  - Employee wage records, 1950-1954 (Box 56A, Folder 4)
  - Employee wage records, 1950-1954 (Box 56B, Folder 1)
  - Employee wage records, 1955-1960 (Box 57A, Folder 1)
  - Employee wage records, 1955-1960 (Box 57B, Folder 1)
  - Employee wage records, 1955-1960 (Box 58A, Folder 1)
  - Employee wage records, 1955-1960 (Box 58B, Folder 1)
  - Employee wage records, September 1969 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Employee wage records, 1970 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
  - Payroll, 1971-1972 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Payroll And Personnel Data, 1969 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Employee wage records - Actors and production crews, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Employee wage records, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - General Ledger, 1968-1969 (Box 61A, Folder 1)
  - Income Allocation, 1971-1972 (Box 61A, Folder 2-5)
  - Insurance - Correspondence, 1954-1956 (Box 61B, Folder 1-2)
  - Office Services Billing reports, 1972 (Box 61B, Folder 3)
  - Office Services Billing reports, 1971 (Box 61B, Folder 4)
  - Operating Ledger, 1967-1968 (Box 61B, Folder 5-6)
  - Payroll summary, 1966-1967 (Box 61B, Folder 7)
  - Proposed Price schedule, 1967-1968 (Box 61B, Folder 8)
  - Report of Fund raising, 1966 (Box 61B, Folder 9)
  - Statements of Financial Position, 1951-1953 (Box 61B, Folder 10)
  - Statements of Financial Position, June 1951 (Box 61B, Folder 11)
  - Statements of Financial Position, June 1952 (Box 61B, Folder 12)
  - Statements of Financial Position - Worksheets, 1953-1955 (Box 61C, Folder 1-2)
  - Statements of Financial Position - Restaurant, 1948-1953 (Box 61C, Folder 3-4)
  - Statements of Financial Position - Theater and School, 1948-1955 (Box 61C, Folder 5-7)
  - Summary of Operations, 1950-1951 (Box 61C, Folder 8)
  - Summary of Operations, 1954-1955 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Summary of Operations, 1967 (April and ten months) (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Tax Returns - Federal quarterly, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Ticketron Sales reports, 1971-1972 (Box 62, Folder 4-5)
  - Tuition Record sheets, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Unemployment reports, 1948-1954 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Wage Tax Instructions and Information, 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Withholding and Wage statements, 1944-1954 (Box 62, Folder 9-11)
  - Withholding and Wage statements, 1956-1959 (Box 63, Folder 1-6)
  - Withholding and Wage statements, 1967-1970 (Box 64, Folder 1-4)
  - Withholding of Occupation Tax certificates, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Withholding of Occupation Tax certificates, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Budget - Cash disbursements, 1966-1967; Oversize (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Budget - Spread sheets, 1964-1965; Oversize (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Budget - General journal, 1969; Oversize (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Budget - Cash receipts deposits distribution register, 1968-1969; Oversize (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Budget - Current activity by source code, August 1972; Oversize (Box 66, Folder 2-3)
  - Budget - General journal, 1968-1969; Oversize (Box 67, Volume 1)
  - Deferred income, 1972-1973; Oversize (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Income allocation, 1972-1973; Oversize (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Payroll Summary, 1967-1970; Oversize (Box 68, Folder 3-4)
  - Schedules of revenues and expenditures, 1971; Oversize (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Stage Door Club employee time sheets, 1972; Oversize (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Statements of operations, 1971-1972; Oversize (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Student Education fund, Oversize (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Theatre income, 1971-1972; Oversize (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Vendor codes, April 1970; Oversize (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Social Security weekly time books, 1954-1956; Oversize (Box 69, Folder 2-3)
  - Source and Class codes, 1972-1973; Oversize (Box 69, Volume 1)
  - General ledger, 1945-1946; Oversize (Box 69, Volume 2)
- Photographs and Negatives, 1935-1993; III.
  This series of photographic images is arranged into four subseries. Each of the subseries are arranged alphabetically. Often there images for an individual or production in several of the four subseries.
  See Also
  See addendum 1 for additional photos.
  - Individual Performers' Photographs, 1.
    Scope and Content Notes
    These photographs are arranged in alphabetical order by last name.
    - Abdam, Gloria (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Abels, Gregory (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Aberlin, Betty (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Abrahams, Joan (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Ackerman, Mary Frances (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Addis, George (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Akalitis, Joanne (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Alber, Fred (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Alber, Freda (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Albert, Will (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Alderson, Christian (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Allen, Albert (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Allen, Jack (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Allen, Penelope (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Alexander, Hugh (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Alexander, Rod (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Altman, Jane (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Alu, Al (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Alzia, Ben (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Anderson, Elaine (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Andrews, Dana (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Andracheck, Wallace (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Apples, Walter (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Arbeit, Herman O. (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Archer, Lynn (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Archer, Richard (Box 70, Folder 26)
    - Argenziano, Carmen (Box 70, Folder 27)
    - Arnett, Warren (Box 70, Folder 28)
    - Atkinso, Brooks (Box 70, Folder 29)
    - Audrachik, Phyllis (Box 70, Folder 30)
    - Athin, Irwin (Box 70, Folder 31)
    - Austin, Elizabeth (Box 70, Folder 32)
    - Bailey, Ann (Box 70, Folder 33)
    - Baker, John (Box 70, Folder 34)
    - Baker, Lenny (Box 70, Folder 35)
    - Baker, Robert (Box 70, Folder 36)
    - Ball, George (Box 70, Folder 37)
    - Ball, William (Box 70, Folder 38)
    - Banick, Gloria Jean (Box 70, Folder 39)
    - Bardwell, Robert (Box 70, Folder 40)
    - Barker, Connie (Box 70, Folder 41)
    - Barley, William (Box 70, Folder 42)
    - Barnes, Emily (Box 70, Folder 43)
    - Barr, Kathy (Box 70, Folder 44)
    - Barrie, Barbara (Box 70, Folder 45)
    - Barouge, Rachelle (Box 70, Folder 46)
    - Barrister, Susan (Box 70, Folder 47)
    - Barton, Lucy (Box 70, Folder 48)
    - Baskin, Billy (Box 70, Folder 49)
    - Baskin, Sammy (Box 70, Folder 50)
    - Bassett, June (Box 70, Folder 51)
    - Batcha, George (Box 70, Folder 52)
    - Bateman, Phyllis (Box 70, Folder 53)
    - Bates, Heddie (Box 70, Folder 54)
    - Battista, Lloyd (Box 70, Folder 55)
    - Bault, George (Box 70, Folder 56)
    - Bazerman, William (Box 70, Folder 57)
    - Beadle, Stanley (Box 70, Folder 58)
    - Beatty, John (Box 70, Folder 59)
    - Bebey, Frank (Box 70, Folder 60)
    - Beck, Morton (Box 70, Folder 61)
    - Becker, Alan (Box 70, Folder 62)
    - Bennett, Hyman (Box 70, Folder 63)
    - Benson, Lucille (Box 70, Folder 64)
    - Berdeshevsky, Margo A. (Box 70, Folder 65)
    - Berkson, Michael (Box 70, Folder 66)
    - Berry, Dawn (Box 70, Folder 67)
    - Billett, Donald (Box 70, Folder 68)
    - Bishop, Sherwood (Box 70, Folder 69)
    - Blaine, Edward (Box 70, Folder 70)
    - Blaxill, Peter (Box 70, Folder 71)
    - Bleviss, Alan (Box 70, Folder 72)
    - Bloch, Barbara (Box 70, Folder 73)
    - Blossom, Robert (Box 70, Folder 74)
    - Blum, Arthur (Box 70, Folder 75)
    - Boem, Earl (Box 70, Folder 76)
    - Bohm, Steve (Box 70, Folder 77)
    - Bonant, Anne (Box 70, Folder 78)
    - Bond, Nancy (Box 70, Folder 79)
    - Booth, Sidney (Box 70, Folder 80)
    - Bonacci, Carmen (Box 70, Folder 81)
    - Bowen, Earl (Box 70, Folder 82)
    - Bowden, Beth (Box 70, Folder 83)
    - Bower, Joan (Box 70, Folder 84)
    - Boyd, Sam (Box 70, Folder 85)
    - Braden, John (Box 70, Folder 86)
    - Bradley, Steve (Box 70, Folder 87)
    - Brandon, Eunice (Box 70, Folder 88)
    - Brassler, Muriel (Box 70, Folder 89)
    - Bray, David (Box 70, Folder 90)
    - Bright, Richard (Box 70, Folder 91)
    - Brinefield, Cleo (Box 70, Folder 92)
    - Brink, Robert (Box 70, Folder 93)
    - Britton, Gary (Box 70, Folder 94)
    - Brockett, Don (Box 70, Folder 95)
    - Brown, Debby (Box 70, Folder 96)
    - Brown, George S. (Box 70, Folder 97)
    - Brown, Graham (Box 70, Folder 98)
    - Brown, Mary Redfern (Box 70, Folder 99)
    - Browning, Robert (Box 70, Folder 100)
    - Bruno, Jean (Box 70, Folder 101)
    - Bruce, Katherine (Box 70, Folder 102)
    - Bruce, Lydia (Box 70, Folder 103)
    - Buck, John (Box 70, Folder 104)
    - Buka, Donald (Box 70, Folder 105)
    - Bugbee, Geneva (Box 70, Folder 106)
    - Bunt, George (Box 70, Folder 107)
    - Burkley, Jay (Box 70, Folder 108)
    - Burgess, Robert (Box 70, Folder 109)
    - Burke, Brendan (Box 70, Folder 110)
    - Bunde, Irene (Box 70, Folder 111)
    - Burleigh, Fred (Box 70, Folder 112)
    - Burns, Barbara (Box 70, Folder 113)
    - Burns, Kitty (Box 70, Folder 114)
    - Busch, Edward (Box 70, Folder 115)
    - Byrd, Anne Gee (Box 70, Folder 116)
    - Byrd, David (Box 70, Folder 117)
    - Caesar, Adolphe (Box 70, Folder 118)
    - Cain, Constance (Box 70, Folder 119)
    - Callahan, Gladys (Box 70, Folder 120)
    - Camlin, Calvert (Box 70, Folder 121)
    - Camp, Helen Page (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Campbell, Carole (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Campbell, Kitty (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Campbell, Owen (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Cantril, Ken (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Cardillo, Bobby (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Cathright, Margaret (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Carey, Helen (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Carney, Josie (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Carney, Kay (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Carlisle, Robert (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Carpenter, Jo (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Carra, Lawrence (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Carroll, Vincent (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Caruso, Barbara (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Carruthers, James (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Cascrotti, Charlene (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Cathell, Margaret (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Causey, Edwin (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Cazale, John (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Chace, Dorothy (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Challingsworth, Elizabeth (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Champion, Gill (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Chapman, Grace (Box 71, Folder 24)
    - Chapman, James (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Chapman, Nancy (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Chapman, Ted (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Chensy, Nancy (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Cherry, Harold (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Childs, Frank (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Cimino, Leonardo (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Claeren, Wayne (Box 71, Folder 32)
    - Claire, Ludi (Box 71, Folder 33)
    - Clark, John (Box 71, Folder 34)
    - Clark, Carolyn (Box 71, Folder 35)
    - Clary, Roy (Box 71, Folder 36)
    - Clodfetter, Jane (Box 71, Folder 37)
    - Cloud, Barbara (Box 71, Folder 38)
    - Clowes, Dudley (Box 71, Folder 39)
    - Cockran, John (Box 71, Folder 40)
    - Code, Grant (Box 71, Folder 41)
    - Cohen, Alvin (Box 71, Folder 42)
    - Colby, Ronald (Box 71, Folder 43)
    - Coleman, Jane (Box 71, Folder 44)
    - Collins,Shirley (Box 71, Folder 45)
    - Colton, Paula (Box 71, Folder 46)
    - Conte, Gino (Box 71, Folder 47)
    - Colby, Ronald (Box 71, Folder 48)
    - Cook, Charles (Box 71, Folder 49)
    - Coppola, Frank (Box 71, Folder 50)
    - Coralian, Ronald (Box 71, Folder 51)
    - Cordic, Rege (Box 71, Folder 52)
    - Cornett, Barbara and Ewell (Box 71, Folder 53)
    - Corot, Suzanne (Box 71, Folder 54)
    - Coryell, Esther Jane (Box 71, Folder 55)
    - Cosgrove, Robert (Box 71, Folder 56)
    - Costopoulos, John (Box 71, Folder 57)
    - Cowan, Irene (Box 71, Folder 58)
    - Cowherd, Ethel (Box 71, Folder 59)
    - Cox, Elise (Box 71, Folder 60)
    - Coyle, Joseph J. (Box 71, Folder 61)
    - Crantz, David (Box 71, Folder 62)
    - Cratty, Barbara (Box 71, Folder 63)
    - Crawford, Colette (Box 71, Folder 64)
    - Crawley, Thomas (Box 71, Folder 65)
    - Cree, Walter (Box 71, Folder 66)
    - Cremini, Robert (Box 71, Folder 67)
    - Crittenden, Ladye (Box 71, Folder 68)
    - Cronyn, Hume and Tandy, Jessica (Box 71, Folder 69)
    - Croydon, Joan (Box 71, Folder 70)
    - Dacey, George (Box 71, Folder 71)
    - Dagney, Robert (Box 71, Folder 72)
    - Dale, Lorna (Box 71, Folder 73)
    - Daly, Tyne (Box 71, Folder 74)
    - Daly, Virginia (Box 71, Folder 75)
    - Darling, Jennifer (Box 71, Folder 76)
    - Dart, Velma (Box 71, Folder 77)
    - Davis, Harold (Box 71, Folder 78)
    - Davis, Jeff (Box 71, Folder 79)
    - Davis, Lenning (Box 71, Folder 80)
    - Davis, Will (Box 71, Folder 81)
    - Dawes, Robyn (Box 71, Folder 82)
    - Dawes, Zita Hill (Box 71, Folder 83)
    - Day, Hope (Box 71, Folder 84)
    - Daykin, Judith (Box 71, Folder 85)
    - Deane, Palmer (Box 71, Folder 86)
    - de Banzie, Lou (Box 71, Folder 87)
    - De Gasper, Virginia (Box 71, Folder 88)
    - De Maio, Peter (Box 71, Folder 89)
    - De Niro, Robert (Box 71, Folder 90)
    - De Paul, Carol (Box 71, Folder 91)
    - de Roy, Jamie (Box 71, Folder 92)
    - Dennis, Tom (Box 71, Folder 93)
    - Detrick, Bruce (Box 71, Folder 94)
    - Devlin, Jay (Box 71, Folder 95)
    - Diamond, Stephanie Cohen (Box 71, Folder 96)
    - Di Cenzo, George (Box 71, Folder 97)
    - Di Geosio, Collete (Box 71, Folder 98)
    - Di Silvio, Natale (Box 71, Folder 99)
    - Dickens, Dean (Box 71, Folder 100)
    - Dine, James (Box 71, Folder 101)
    - Dixon, Oliver (Box 71, Folder 102)
    - Disney, Will (Box 71, Folder 103)
    - Dobkin, Ronald (Box 71, Folder 104)
    - Dobrin, Ron (Box 71, Folder 105)
    - Dodge, Priscilla (Box 71, Folder 106)
    - Doescher, Margaret (Box 71, Folder 107)
    - Dolokov, Adele (Box 71, Folder 108)
    - Don, Carl (Box 71, Folder 109)
    - Donahue, Mary Jane (Box 71, Folder 110)
    - Donahue, Nancy (Box 71, Folder 111)
    - Dorin, Phoebe (Box 71, Folder 112)
    - Doyle, Jay (Box 71, Folder 113)
    - Dozer, Carl (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Dement, Tom (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Drake, Eloise (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Draper, Paul (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Dremeck, W.P. (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Dress, Michael (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Drisch, Rusell (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Driscoll, Ann (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Drexel, Todd (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - Ducey, Mary Evelyn (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Dunston, Tallye (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Duprey, Bruce (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - Dunlap, Pamela (Box 72, Folder 13)
    - Durning, Charles (Box 72, Folder 14)
    - Durrell, Michael (Box 72, Folder 15)
    - Dysart, Richard (Box 72, Folder 16)
    - Edmunds, Dallas (Box 72, Folder 17)
    - Efron, Marshal (Box 72, Folder 18)
    - Eis, Elizabeth (Box 72, Folder 19)
    - Elbaum, Nat (Box 72, Folder 20)
    - Eldes, Elman (Box 72, Folder 21)
    - Elm, Sandra (Box 72, Folder 22)
    - Endes, Joe (Box 72, Folder 23)
    - Engle, Bernie (Box 72, Folder 24)
    - Engle, Harriet (Box 72, Folder 25)
    - Estrin, Marc (Box 72, Folder 26)
    - Eyrick, George (Box 72, Folder 27)
    - Eythe, Bill (Box 72, Folder 28)
    - Fagan, Norman (Box 72, Folder 29)
    - Fahey, Lee Ann (Box 72, Folder 30)
    - Fancy, Richard (Box 72, Folder 31)
    - Fausold, Patricia (Box 72, Folder 32)
    - Feather, Ruth (Box 72, Folder 33)
    - Fedoroff, George (Box 72, Folder 34)
    - Feiner, Marcelle (Box 72, Folder 35)
    - Feldman, Leonard (Box 72, Folder 36)
    - Felser, Marcie (Box 72, Folder 37)
    - Fenwick, Don (Box 72, Folder 38)
    - Ferguson, Phyllis (Box 72, Folder 39)
    - Finkel, Marjorie (Box 72, Folder 40)
    - Finkel, Robert (Box 72, Folder 41)
    - Fischer, Ruth (Box 72, Folder 42)
    - Fisher, Jules (Box 72, Folder 43)
    - Fisher, Paul (Box 72, Folder 44)
    - Flaherty, Joseph (Box 72, Folder 45)
    - Fleming, Elizabeth (Box 72, Folder 46)
    - Fleming, Olive (Box 72, Folder 47)
    - Ford, William (Box 72, Folder 48)
    - Foster, Herbert (Box 72, Folder 49)
    - Foster, Preston (Box 72, Folder 50)
    - Fowler, Clement (Box 72, Folder 51)
    - Fox, Richard (Box 72, Folder 52)
    - Francisco, William (Box 72, Folder 53)